

## Competences

**TypeScript** 

**HTML** 

CSS/SCSS

**Angular** 

React

**NgRx** 

**Redux** 

**ASP.NET Core** 

**Node**|S

**NestJS** 

# Contact

★ Budapest

**L** +36 20 234 8599

■ szoke.viktor95@gmail.com

# VIKTOR SZŐKE

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

#### Introduction

My name is Viktor Szőke and I have been studying Computer Engineering at Budapest University of Technology and Economics. My main interests are web- and mobile app development, but I am also interested in UX/UI design.

I have 4 years experience as a Frontend Developer.

# Experience

2021 - Present SnapSoft

Frontend Developer, Budapest
I work here mainly as a frontend developer, but sometimes I do backend stuff. My main tasks included creating, testing and communicating with the client. I used the following technologies: Angular, Swagger, Cypress, Nest|S, RX|S, Redux, TypeScript

**2018 - 2021 EN-CO Software Kft.** 

Frontend Developer, Budapest
I worked here as a frontend developer and as a team leader. My main tasks included creating, testing and write documentation. I also participated in mentoring students and delegating tasks. I used the following technologies: Angular, ASP.NET Core, Swagger, Cypress, NodeJS, RXJS, Redux, TypeScript

**2017 - 2017** Eastron Kft.

Software Tester, Budapest
I worked here as a manual software tester.
This was a student work for summer.

Education

2020 - 2022 Budapest University of Technologies and

Economics (MSc)

2015 - 2020 Budapest University of Technologies and

**Economics (BSc)** 

## Languages

**Hungarian - Native** 

**English - B2 Certificate**